Hi, in this lesson, I want to show you how to use a common feature from Windyorf.
This feature lets you write or edit code inside your editor using natural language.
It's built for some quick changes within a single file, keeping your focus and in the
flow.
As there are two key points how to use this feature, as there is a scope, it works best
for changes in the file you're working on, it's not for full project changes, it's for changes
which you want to apply directly in this file in a current file.
And you also can use models, so there are at least of models are optimized for changes within
a single file, or you can use them.
The first one, Windyorf Fast is free, so you can use it.
There are a few options how you can use this feature, or generate code and for edit code.
If you want to edit the existing code you just selected, press common plus i if you
don't mark, or you can use control plus i if you're on Windows or Linux, and you can ask some
question or write the prompt, and it will be related to the selected part of code it will
be as a contact, so AI will update the current code, but if you want to, for example, generate
a new code in some exact place, you can just put your core source right here, you can
click common i again, and you can write your prompt, and it will generate a new code and place
it here.
So this is a few options how you can use it.
Let me show you an example, we have this part of code, and I will ask Windyorf to optimize
it, optimize it, and I will show you how we can work with it.
So you see it really optimize it, we have now two lines, but it's not really clear.
So I can ask some follow-up questions, for example, so just use switch case, okay, but
they still don't like, the calculation is too complex to meet to understand, for example,
corrects all the way, sorry, I did accept it, so I can just complete common path that,
it will back, and it will just ask my follow-up question, yep, now it looks more simple,
I can click accept, and we see, in case if it's 01, it's very weak, so it's much more clear
to me, so of course longer, so we can ask both, optimize it, like if it's between 01 or between
two and three, so it's up for you.
Also you can use common in the terminal, the same combination of keys to run it, and for
example, what I can ask, how I can run this script, now you see the common, the not, and
the file name, but it won't work because we use the new way of imports, null of files, and
it doesn't work, we also might use the old not version, but we wrote this code not running
it in terminal, I just wanted to show you that it's possible and that the result is working,
so but we're not going to run it, but you can also reject it or accept or just run the
command, I'm going to reject it, okay, I'll let's do some summary, so the command feature
is great for, we call it edits or some generation in the current trial, it also understands
what is your file, it's about, because it has a context, you can give some follow-up prompt
or awesome follow-up questions to improve the result of the generation, and it also works
in terminal to create some CLI commands, also if you don't know how to use git commands,
you can also ask it, so about how, so in general, command feature help you to make focus
on your changes in the flow in your file, so without losing the context, okay, I hope
it was useful for you and still in the next reference.